It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
That's right.
そうだよね
We're nervous too.
俺らも緊張してるから
We're more nervous, right?
俺らの方が緊張してるでしょ?
That's right.
そうですよね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's okay, don't be nervous.
緊張しなくて大丈夫
from now.
今から
I'm going to go into the room now and explain the story in detail.
今からお話を部屋に入って詳しくしていきます
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
Please apply today.
今日応募してきてもらって
Are you interested in doing something?
何 かするの興味あって?
I'm interested.
興味はあります
Gear location?
ギアロケ?
Is there a genre you want to go to?
何か行きたいジャンルとか?
I like cute idols.
可愛いアイドルが好きです
Do you like cute idols?
可愛いアイドルが好き?
I like idols.
アイドル好きです
Who are you?
誰ですか?
Like Nogizaka.
のぎザカとか
Sakane?
サカネ?
yes.
はい
Ah, but Isou.
あ、でもイソウ
It's really cool.
めちゃめちゃイソウですね
Let's get into a fight.
喧嘩入らせて
That's fine.
いいです
Sorry, I took a picture.
ごめんね、撮っちゃって
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I think you're nervous.
緊張してると思うけどね
Are you doing anything now?
今何かやってるの?
Entertainment, etc.
芸能とか
I'm currently an underground idol.
今、地下アイドルをやってます
Oh no.
やば
You're already doing it.
もうやってるんですね
It's cute.
可愛いもんね
That's why.
だからいかん
Do you like idols?
アイドル好きなの?
I like idols.
アイドル好きです
What kind of idol do you like?
どういうアイドルが好きなの?
Like a certain group.
あるグループさんとか
Mr. Nogizaka.
ノギザカさん
It's Isou.
イソウですね
It's Nogizaka, right?
ノギザカでしょ
ERROR
むしろ研究生
む し ろ
Is it different?
違うの?
Do you want to join Nogizaka?
ノギザカ入りたいとかある?
I want to enter.
入りたいです
I see.
なるほど
I think we should have a quick meeting and talk about work.
軽く打ち合わせして、仕事のことを話そうかなみたいな
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
時間大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You're nervous.
緊張してるね
Let's relax.
リラックスしちゃおう
Relax, relax.
リラックスして、リラックス
This guy is cool, isn't he?
かっこいいでしょ、この人
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
Don't be nervous.
緊 張しないで
It makes me nervous.
緊張するよね
It's not scary.
怖くはない
I hope you enjoy it.
楽しんがってね
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
That's right.
そうだよね
I often apply for jobs myself.
結構自分で応募とかしてるし
sometimes.
たまに
sometimes?
たまに?
If it's this cute, it won't be a problem if it sells.
こんなに可愛かったら売れるのも時間が問題ない
I wonder what it is.
どうなんだろう
We almost arrived at the studio.
そろそろスタジオまで着いたんですよ
I'm nervous.
緊張します
That's right.
そうだよね
It's cute.
可愛いですね
There's nothing weird about that,
変なことは別にあれじゃないから、
I just want to do something light, like talk or something.
普通にお話とかさ、 軽く何かしたいと思ってるだけ
I know you're nervous, but relax.
緊張すると思うけど、 リラックスしてさ、
Let's do our best.
頑張っていこう
The nape of the neck, the nape of the neck, the nape of the neck is beautiful.
うなじが、うなじが、 うなじがきれい
Oh no.
やば
Your nose is white.
鼻白いですね
ERROR
すごい白い
good?
いい?
Her ears are also really cute.
耳もめっちゃ可愛いですよね
That's dangerous.
やばいよね
It's a bit of a studio.
ちょっとスタジオかね
studio.
スタジオ
A little studio.
ちょっとスタジオ
Just over here.
ちょっとこっちに
Look at your hands.
手を見て
I'm nervous.
緊張して
My hands are shaking.
手震えてますね
Do you want to eat strawberries?
いちご食べる?
Do you like strawberries?
いちご好き?
Don't eat, don't eat.
食べな、食べな
Ichigo is happy.
喜んじゃって、いちごが
ERROR
いちごがね
cute.
可愛い
Is it okay if I take this?
これ取っちゃって大丈夫?
Because it is necessary for the examination.
審査で必要だから
cute.
可愛い
Strawberries look good on you.
いちごが似合いますね
strawberry?
い ちご?
Let yourself eat.
食べる自分で、食べさせる
Can I eat it?
食べていい?
Don't eat, don't eat.
食べな、食べな
eat.
食べる
It's cute.
可愛いね
delicious?
美味しい?
delicious.
美味しい
It's cute.
可愛いね
Will this ever be photographed on camera?
これでカメラで撮られることある?
do not have.
ない
I don't think so.
ないと思う
What do you mean you don't think so?
ないと思うってどういうこと?
ERROR
撮った?
Did you take a picture?
What are you saying?
何 か言ってんの?
With love.
愛 でね
You said that earlier.
言ってたね、さっき
That's what he said.
言ってた
That's why it's cute.
だから可愛いんだね
My skin is so tight.
肌がピチピチだな
It's squishy.
ぷにぷにじゃん
Your skin is white.
肌白いよね
Did you notice?
気をついた?
Because I'm scared.
怖がってるから
That's no good.
ダ メだよ
Let's hear some things.
いろいろ聞こうよ
How old are you now?
今いくつですか?
I'm 18 now.
今18です
That's nice.
いいですね
Are you going to school now?
今、学校行ってるの?
I will graduate next year.
来年卒業します
What do you like most?
一番好きな?
my favorite
一 番好き
Na.
な
Is there someone you like?
好 きな人いるの?
I like Nogizaka.
乃木坂さんが好き
Oh, Nogizaka?
あ、乃木坂か
Who do you like?
誰が好きとか?
Asuka Saito.
斎藤アスカル
It's cute.
可愛いもんね
I haven't lost at all.
全然負けてないですよ
Asukaru Saito is cute.
斎藤アスカル可愛いよ
Really?
本当に?
Good style.
スタイルいいし
Are you doing any live shows?
ライブとかやってんすか?
Often on weekends.
週末によく
What is it?
どうなんだ?
Can I go?
行っていい?
Ah, it seems no good.
あ、ダメみたい
No?
ダ メ?
It seemed like no good now.
ダメっぽかった、今
I'm going to the study session.
学 習会行くよ、俺
Is it okay to go?
行 っていい?
Do you mean go?
行 って んの?
I don't know.
分かんない
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
What do you mean I don't understand?
分かんないってなんだよ
That's so good.
そんなにいいじゃん
so.
そんなに
Like an underground idol?
地下アイドル的な?
I'm too nervous.
緊張しすぎよ
緊張?
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Wait a minute, can I get you something?
ちょっと待って、いいの持ってくる?
Asuka Saito.
斎藤アスカル
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Have you ever had alcohol?
お酒飲んだことあるの?
Because it makes me nervous.
緊張するから
Maybe you can relax a little?
ちょっとね、リラックスかもいいんじゃない?
Shall we have a drink together?
一緒に飲もうか
Have you ever had it?
飲んだことある?
Alcohol.
お酒
Only once.
一回だけ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Can I drink it?
飲める?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Shall we drink?
飲んじゃう?
It's like juice.
ジュースみたいなもんだから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
cheers.
乾杯
Is it okay?
いいの?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Let's keep it a secret.
内緒にしよう
内 緒にしよう
Who do you usually work with?
普段は誰と動かしてるの?
A cafe in Harajuku.
原宿でカフェの
a ...
あ ...
Can I go?
行っていい?
I don't know.
分かんない
People say they don't understand everything.
全部分かんないって言われるね
That's right.
そうなんだ
I'm sure there will be quite a few fan meetings going on.
結構なんかファン会とか来るんじゃない?
surely.
確かに
What do idol fans expect?
アイドルファンのファンが期待するの?
It won't come.
来ない
I didn't say that.
言ってないんだ
Shall I go to the bodyguard?
俺ボディガード行くよ?
Well, today, you came to apply.
まあでも今日ね、応募に来てくれてさ
I'm happy though.
嬉しいんだけどさ
Today I'm doing some cosplay.
今日はコスプレとかね
I always have someone do it for me.
いつもね、してもらったり
Also, a swimsuit.
あと 水着をね
They also have swimsuits.
水着もあるんだしけ
Have you ever worn a swimsuit?
水着着たことあります?
There are swimsuits.
水着あります
be?
ある?
Sukumizu.
すくみず
It's school, right?
学校でしょ
It's like I want you to give me some money and give me some money.
シャネをシャネしてご遣いしてもらいたいなーみたいな感じ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそう そう
Can I drink it?
飲んでいいですか?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Alcohol?
お酒?
Isn't it a little tight?
なんか きつくない?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Do you need some money?
お金はちょっと必要だったりするの?
need.
必要
It's the recruitment process.
募集過程ね
I guess I need some money.
ちょっといろいろお金が必要かな
Well, today, I'm spending money.
まあまあ今日ね、お金使いね
Take it with you.
持 って ね
Please take it home.
持って帰ってもらってね
Grab the dog.
犬をつかめ
He's a suspicious person though.
怪しい人だけどね
Not too much, don't feel anxious.
あんまりね、不安な思わないで
That's right, that's right.
そうだね、そうだね
It's still a bit stiff, though.
ちょっとまだね、凝り固まってるから
It's good for things like language and speaking.
言語系とかでさ、 喋りとかもいいから
I feel like I need to relax a little more.
あとちょっとリラックスしてほしいなーみたいな
I want you to relax.
リラックスしてほしい
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
So cute.
かわいいっすね
Don't be nervous, okay?
緊張しないでいい?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Eh, is it okay to wear a swimsuit today?
え、今日水着とか大丈夫?
I think I'd like to take some photos at least once.
一回ちょっと写真とか撮りたいなと思うんだけど
Can you go?
いける?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
See you later.
ちょっと後でじゃあ
My body is hot.
体熱いよ
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
It's really hot, isn't it?
めっちゃ熱いでしょ
If it's too hot, you'll suffer from heat illness.
あんまり熱いと熱調症とか大変だからさ
I was just fluttering around a bit.
ちょっと俺がパタパタしてて
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
I'll spin it.
俺は紡いとくから
I just want to cool it down.
冷やしてあげたいだけだよ
Cool your body
体を冷やしてあ
I want to get it.
げ たい
Do you want a cold?
風邪欲しいですか?
It feels like it's flopping.
パタパタって感じ
What kind of costumes do idols usually wear?
アイドル普段どんな感じの衣装なの?
Furifuri or something.
フリフリとか
Ah, that's right.
あーそうなんだ
Furifuri.
フリフリ
It's quite frilly-like.
結構フリフリみたいな
Is it like frilly clothes?
服フリフリみたいな感じ?
How frilly?
どんぐらいフリフリ?
Furifuri?
フリフリ?
This much frilly?
こんぐらいフリフリ?
This is really frilly.
これめっちゃフリフリだよね
It's growing.
伸びるね
I thought I'd like to see some frilly stuff.
ちょっとフリフリ見たいなって思って
You might be looking here.
ここ見てるかも
Because I want to see this.
ここ見たいから
Stretch this out a little bit.
ちょっと一回ここ伸ばして
Because I want to show it to the camera.
カメラに見せたいから
Please let me get away with it once.
一回手抜けてもらって
It's frilly.
フ リフリだね
That's good, that's good.
いいですね、いいですね
I see.
なるほど
You're young.
若いね
若いですね
I couldn't take a picture right now.
ちょっと今撮れなかった
Just one more time here.
もう一回ちょっとここだけね
Only here?
ここだけ?
Only here.
ここだけ
I have to stretch it.
伸ばさないと
Just drink this.
ちょっとこれ飲みな
I'm nervous.
緊張して
This is trendy right now.
これ今流行りなの
fashion?
流行り?
The design is cute.
可愛いね、デザイン
cute?
可愛 い?
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
I won't do anything now.
何のことしないよ、今
I'm nervous.
緊張して
Because it's a check.
チェックだから
Normally.
普 通に
Just check.
ちょっと チェック
Your neck is beautiful.
首筋が綺麗だよね
Check out a few different places.
ちょっと色んなところチェックして
I have to talk comprehensively.
総合的に話しなきゃ
The nape of your neck?
首筋?
I see.
なるほどね
Ah, the nape of my neck.
あ、うなじが
The nape of your neck is beautiful.
うなじが綺麗だね
Would you like to stand up for a moment?
ちょっと立ってみる?
One time I went around as a crew member like an idol.
一回なんかアイドルっぽく クルーって回ったやつ
Usual.
普段の
Something like meow.
なんかニャンみたいな
It's like a stage.
ステージみたいな
cute!
可愛い!
Are you doing it?
やってんの?
this.
これ
cute!
可愛 い!
Do you want to pussies?
ニャンニャンってしたい?
Meow meow.
ニャンニャン
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
What about Furifuri Nyan?
フリフリニャンは?
Here, on my own, I stretch out my frilly nyan and look at it frilly.
ここさ、自分でさ、 フリフリニャンって伸ばして フリフリ見
Let me.
せて
It's called frifurinyan.
フ リフリニャンって
Just a little bit, if you look like an idol,
ちょっとだけさ、アイドルっぽくなったら、
Meow, on the front side.
ニャンってさ、前側で
Meow.
ニャンって
I'm going to check Furifuri.
フリフリチェックいくね
I see.
なるほどね
Nice, nice.
いい ね、いいね
My clothes are a little off.
服 がちょっとね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Don't be nervous.
緊張しないで
Okay, okay.
いい よ、 いいよ
Hey, hey.
ちょっと、ちょっと
Fluffy.
フ リフリして
Hey, swimsuit.
ちょっと、水着
Do you have a swimsuit?
水着ある?
Would you like to take a look?
ちょっと見ていきますか
Isn't the swimsuit nice?
水着いいでしょ?
Swimsuit.
水着
I put it out, but it wasn't there.
出したんですけど、なかったっすね
Wasn't there?
なかったっけ?
Sorry.
すいません
It's no good.
だめなんだよ
There wasn't, but another.
なかったのに、別の
Well, kind of.
まあ、なんか
Looks like Agitneph.
アジトニーフっぽいし
I'd like to check out Furifuri a little more.
もうちょっとだけ、 フリフリのチェックをしたいんですよね
Isn't this also frilly?
ここもフリフリじゃないですか
I want to keep this a little longer.
これもうちょっとキープしたい
Sorry if it's a substitute for a swimsuit.
水着の代わりだと、ごめんね
You don't know, right?
わかんないでしょ?
oh yeah.
そうそう
nice.
いいね
That's not good enough.
上だめなんだ、あれなんて
I see.
そっか
It's hot, isn't it?
暑いでしょ、やばいからさ
Fluttering.
ひらひらね
Yes, fluttering is important.
そう、ひらひら大事
The style is really nice.
スタイルめっちゃいい
How are you feeling?
気分どうしたの?
I'll do something weird.
変なことしちゃうよ
Sorry for a second.
ちょっと、ごめん
Swimsuits, that's why they're so important.
水着、あれだから大事だから
Don't try too hard today.
今日、頑張りしないで
Could you please hold it a little longer?
もうちょっとキープしてくれない?
Shall we give it a try?
ちょっとやってみようか
Because it's latent.
潜在だから
Shall we give it a try?
ちょっとやってみようか
Let's give it a try.
ちょっとやってみよう
Soooo beautiful.
すっげえ綺麗
Good, good.
いいね、いいね
Eh, amazing.
えー、すごい
Because it's a swimsuit.
水着だからね
Open it a little more.
もうちょっと開けて
It's cute.
かわいいね
amazing.
すごい
That's amazing.
すごいな
You've worked hard so far.
ここまで、頑張ってくれてるから
First, the chalet.
先に、シャレーをね
It looks like a chalet.
シャレーそうだよ
Chalet.
シャレー
For now, at this stage.
とりあえずね、ここの段階で
Okay, okay.
いい よ、いいよ
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
Because you're working hard.
頑張ってくれてるから
good.
よかった
Of course, of course.
もちろん、もちろん
Because I worked hard.
頑張ったからね
Is this all you need?
このだけでいいの?
If you put a little more effort into your swimsuit,
もうちょっと、 水着とか、 頑張ってくれたら、
I guess I'll add a little more.
もうちょっとプラスするかな
I guess I'll add it.
プラスするかな
Do you want to try it some more?
もうちょっとやってみる?
Shall we try it?
やってみようか
I'll do it for a while.
ちょっとやるね
Stroke the texture like this.
質感をこう撫でて
There's a sense of size, or rather, a sense of swimsuit size.
なんか、サイズ感っていうか、 水着のサイズ感とかあるじゃん
This can be measured.
これ、測れるからさ
Because it can be measured.
測定できるから
Have you ever measured it?
測ったことある?
No.
ないです
Because I can.
でき るから
How many cups?
何カップなの?
In terms of size.
サ イズ的には
C?
Cか
Is that about it?
そんぐらいですか?
I just don't understand.
ちょっと分かんないんで
what happened?
どう したの?
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
It's okay.
ちょっと大丈夫
Feeling of size.
サイズ感
Can you step out for a moment?
一回ちょっと抜けますか
So far.
ここまではね
So, how about a swimsuit?
じゃあ、 水着になっちゃう?
I agree.
そうですね
That's amazing.
すごいね
Isn't it dangerous?
やばくね?
It's not posing, it's more like a gravure photo.
ポージングじゃなくて、 グラビアみたいな感じです
This is absolutely essential.
絶対これ必須だ
Would you like to try it?
やってみる?
hang on.
待って
Wow, what is this?
うわ、何これ?
cute.
かわいい
what?
何?
Did you do it?
やってた?
Haven't you done it?
やってない?
Awesome, so cute.
すごい、かわいい
Hey, here.
ちょっと、ここ
amazing.
すごい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
No?
ダメ?
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Is the right side weak?
右は弱いの?
What about the left?
左は?
Try to see which one is weaker.
どっちが弱いか試して
Check check.
チェックチェック
Which one?
どっち?
Both.
どっちも
Are you facing backwards?
後ろ向いてるでしょ?
There is.
あるじゃん
gravure.
グラビアの
That's good.
いい ですね
Looks like gravure
グラビアっぽく
difference.
さ
That's right.
そう いうの
This is important.
これ大事
oh yeah.
そうそう
Let's do this a little more.
もうちょっとこう
Give me a ride.
乗せちゃって
cute.
かわいい
I was doing gravure.
グラビア、やってた
Today's swimsuits are terrorism.
今の水着って、テロテロ
oh yeah.
そうそう
Terror terrorist.
テロテロ
About expansion and contraction.
伸縮ぐらい
nice.
いい ね
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Did you do that?
そうしたの?
質感
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Because it's a swimsuit.
水着だから
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's a bit of a texture, isn't it?
ちょっと、質感でしょ?
Of underwear.
下着の
The texture of the swimsuit is nice.
水着の質感が、 いい なっていう
I think there is a material that suits your body.
自分にさ、体に合ってる 材質とかあると思うから
I agree.
そうだ ね
It smells.
匂いね
I just need the smell.
匂いだけ必要だから
The smell of this swimsuit.
この水着の匂い
oh yeah.
そうそう
I want to scare you.
かかしたいで
What kind of smell?
どんな匂い?
Smells nice.
いい匂い
amazing.
すごい
Amazing, smooth.
すごい、すべすべ
Smooth.
すべすべ
Are you okay.
大丈夫
That's right.
そっかそっか
amazing.
すごい
It's so amazing.
めちゃくちゃすごい
Plus?
プラスで?
You don't need anything else, right?
他に必要ないでしょ?
nice.
いいね
Because it's hard.
大変だから
Because it's hard
hey.
ね
Just don't touch me.
ちょっと 一緒に触るな
This is for later.
これ、後でね
oh yeah.
そうそう
But, look.
でも、ほら
I want to see it.
見たい
Well, I wonder what it is.
まあ、何だろう
Like a body check.
体チェックみたいな
That's a fancy sentence.
洒落文ね
Hidden
隠
You can do it.
して ていいから
For now, let's try removing this.
とりあえず、これを一回外してみようか
Shall I try removing it once?
一回外してみようか
I agree.
そうだね
Oh, that's amazing.
おお、すごい
Just a finger, a finger.
ちょっと指、指
Or two.
何 か2本とかで
Point, point.
指、指
Two, two.
2本、2本
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうだね
It's okay if you don't have two, right?
2つなかったら大丈夫でしょ?
cute.
かわいい
amazing.
すごい
Ordinary.
普通の
I can't see it at all.
全然見えない
You can't see it, right?
見えないでしょ?
Ordinary.
普通の
Let's just turn it around a little bit.
ちょっとだけこう、回してみようか
oh yeah.
そうそう
Turn it a little more.
もうちょっと回して
oh yeah.
そうそう
ah.
ああ
That's amazing.
すごいね
Hands are clean.
手、きれい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
I'm glad it happened now.
今のよかった
Just a little more.
もうちょっと
oh yeah.
そうそう
Well then, thank you for your hard work.
じゃあさ、頑張ってくれたからさ
Let's talk about puns again.
ちょっと、シャレの方をまた
I think it's supposed to be.
はずみたいと思うんですけど
It's okay, it's okay.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん
I'm here for the money.
僕はあの、ここでお金の
A beautiful wave.
き れいなおよぐんで
Stretch out your hand.
手伸ばして
Wow, that's amazing.
え、すごい
so?
そんなに?
You can catch it yourself.
掴み取りは自分で
That's good.
いいよね
You want a joke, right?
シャレ欲しいでしょ?
copper?
どう?
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
This is different.
これは別に
Because it's funny.
シャレだから
It's not money.
お金じゃない
No more.
これ以上は
Okay, okay.
じゃあ、わかりました
Yes, then now.
はい、じゃあもう
This is normal.
もうこれ、通常します
Okay, be normal.
いいよ、普通に
You know, it's hard.
ほら、大変だから
It's really impossible, like this.
本当は無理よ、こんな
Swimsuits, etc.
水着とか
so?
そんなに?
Impossible, but impossible.
無理、無理けど
But it's impossible if you don't accept it.
でも、 受け取らないと無理だよ
Stretch out your hand.
手伸ばして
oh yeah.
そうそう
Hands, hands.
手、手
oh yeah.
そうそう
Isn't it difficult?
大変なんでしょ?
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
It's totally fine.
全然いいよ
Hey, so, hey, it's kind of like that, well,
ちょっと、だから ちょっと、なんかそういう まあ、
Can I do a body check or something?
なんか 体チェックとかしていい?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Taste, taste.
味ね、味ね
Taste, you need taste.
味、味必要だよ
Yeah.
うん
taste.
味
Please put this down.
これ置いてくれ
I'll give it to you later.
後であげるからね
Taste, taste, taste.
味、味、味
Please sit down.
座ってもらって
座 ってもらって
Taste, taste.
味、味
Okay.
いいよ
Because I can't give you money.
お金渡せないから
If you don't like it that much.
あんま嫌がると
You know what?
わかるでしょ
If you don't like it and can't get a little bit of it, you won't be able to give them all your money.
嫌がって、ちょっと 取れないとお金全部 渡せなくなるから
Hey, do your best.
ちょっと、頑張って
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい、すごい
That's right.
そうだ
The softness of my own lips.
自分ついてた唇の 柔らかさが
Don't kiss me.
キスじゃないで
It's not a kiss.
キスじゃない
キスじゃないよ